theartofbooks.com 2018-03-24

# ZOOBILEE collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners and affiliates, including information about your use of the products and services that we offer.

                                         PRIVACY POLICY
        ZOOBILEE is committed to protecting your privacy and safety rights while purchasing
and using our products and services.
Note to Facebook. LinkedIn and Other Social Media Users
        When visiting our Facebook page, LinkedIn profile or other page on social media
websites, and when posting information to or otherwise communicating via that page, your
activities online are subject to the Privacy Policy of that social media website, which may
contain terms and conditions different from ZOOBILEE’s Privacy Policy. Please see the
following pages for further details:
    •   http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy (Facebook’s Privacy Policy);
    •   http://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv (LinkedIn’s Privacy
        Policy);
    •   https://twitter.com/privacy (Twitter’s Privacy Policy);
    •   https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy (ZenDesk’s Privacy Policy); and
    •   https://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy (Google+’s Privacy Policy).
What This Privacy Policy Covers
    !   This policy covers how ZOOBILEE treats personal information that ZOOBILEE collects
        and receives, including information related to any products and services available on
        this Website. Personal information is defined as information about you that is
        personally identifiable, such as your name, mailing address, email address, or other
        contact information, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
    !   This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ZOOBILEE does not own
        or control or to people that ZOOBILEE does not employ or manage.
    !   This policy does not apply to non-personal information − data in a form that does not
        permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer,
        and disclose non-personal information for any lawful purpose.
Information Collection and Use
    !   You can generally visit our Website without revealing any personal information about
        yourself.
    !   ZOOBILEE collects personal information when you register or create a ZOOBILEE
        account, purchase a product from ZOOBILEE, when you use any of ZOOBILEE’s
        online services, and when you enter ZOOBILEE promotions, discounts or special offer
        codes.
    !   When you register or create a ZOOBILEE account, we ask for information such as
        your ZOOBILEE username and password as well as your name, e-mail address, zip
        code, and contact information. Once you register with ZOOBILEE, you are not
        anonymous to us.
    !   When you register or create a ZOOBILEE account, we also ask for your username
        and password for each account you establish on eBay, Amazon or any other online
        platform on which you are currently selling merchandise, your status on each online
        platform, and other matters.
    !   ZOOBILEE collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our
        business partners and affiliates, including information about your use of the products
        and services that we offer.

   !  ZOOBILEE also collects information about your transactions on eBay, Amazon or any
      other online platform on which you are currently selling merchandise as part of your
      using our Services.
   !  ZOOBILEE may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from
      your browser, including your IP address, ZOOBILEE cookie information, and the page
      you request.
   !  ZOOBILEE uses information for the following general purposes: to customize our
      website, advertising and content; to fulfill your requests for products and services; to
      improve our services and customer relations; to contact you; to comply with any and
      all laws, rules and regulations that apply to ZOOBILEE or our Services; and to
      conduct research.
Minors
   !  Persons under the age of 13 may not purchase ZOOBILEE’s products or services. For
      products or services offered online, via Skype or e-mail, we ask that minors have a
      parent or guardian create a ZOOBILEE account that will serve as a family account.
      For e-mail only plans, we ask that a parent or guardian serve as billing contact for
      the account.
   !  ZOOBILEE will not contact persons under the age of 13 for marketing purposes
      without a parent’s permission.
   !  ZOOBILEE does not ask persons under the age of 13 for more personal information,
      as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to use a given product
      or service under the family account.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
   !  ZOOBILEE does not sell, rent, or share personal information about you with other
      people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services that you have
      requested, when we have your permission, and under the following circumstances:
                  !   We provide the information to trusted partners and affiliates who work
                      on behalf of or with ZOOBILEE. These companies may use your
                      personal information to help ZOOBILEE communicate with you about
                      offers from ZOOBILEE and our marketing partners and affiliates.
                      However, these companies do not have any independent right to share
                      this information;
                  !   We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to
                      establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims;
                  !   We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate,
                      prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud,
                      situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any
                      person, violations of ZOOBILEE’s Terms of Service, or as otherwise
                      required by law;
                  !   ZOOBILEE may display targeted advertisements based on personal
                      information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume
                      that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the
                      targeting criteria.
                  !   ZOOBILEE will not provide any personal information to the advertiser
                      when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting
                      with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the
                      advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting
                      criteria used to display the ad.

                  !   We will transfer information about you to our successors and assigns if
                      ZOOBILEE is acquired by or merged with another company, or if
                      ZOOBILEE sells all or substantially all of its assets to another company,
                      or if a controlling interest in ZOOBILEE is transferred or sold to another
                      company. In this event, ZOOBILEE will notify you before more
                      information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a
                      different privacy policy.
Cookies
   !  ZOOBILEE may set and access cookies on your computer.
   !  ZOOBILEE may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages
      set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies
      is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies
      do not have access to ZOOBILEE’s cookies.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information
   !  You can edit your ZOOBILEE account information at any time.
   !  We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to ZOOBILEE, such
      as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters, which are
      considered part of your ZOOBILEE account, without offering you the opportunity to
      opt-out of receiving them.
   !  You can choose to have ZOOBILEE delete your record after account cancellation.
      Some information may remain archived in our system records after your account has
      been deleted.
Confidentiality and Security
   !  We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe
      reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or
      services to you or in order to do their jobs.
   !  We have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect personal
      information about you.
   !  Your ZOOBILEE account information is password-protected.
   !  In certain areas ZOOBILEE uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect
      sensitive data transmissions.
   !  ZOOBILEE encourages our clients to use SSH and SCP (secure Telnet and FTP)
      programs in order to better safeguard customer data.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
   !  ZOOBILEE may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the
      way we treat personal information by posting a notice to our Website or by sending a
      notice to the primary email address specified in your ZOOBILEE account.
For California Users
   •      The California Civil Code requires a business with whom a California resident has
          an established business relationship to disclose to such residents, upon their
          request: (1) the types of personal information the business shares with third
          parties for the third party’s marketing purposes, and (2) the identities of the third
          parties with whom the business has shared this information during the
          immediately preceding calendar year.
   •      If you are a California resident, and would like to make such a request, please
          submit your request via email to PRIVACY@ZOOBILEE.COM.

Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at PRIVACY@ZOOBILEE.COM.
